Hello my name is Radhika Arora and
currently I am pursuing PGDM from
FIIB and I got place in ICICI Labar as
a Risk Analyst talking about
its profile for underwriting how did
FIIB's resources and specific
programs help you secure your
placement at ICICI Labad so talking
about FIIB placement cell was it was
instrumental in helping me secure my
position at ICICI Labad the institute
focus on developing industry relevant
skills through programs like mock
interviews, aptitude training and case
study workshops
addition network opportunities through guest
lectures and alumnae interaction help me
understand the industry's expectations
overall considering ICICI Labar focus on
insurance solutions how do you plan to
contribute to this sector based on the
skills you develop at FIIB so talking
about FIIB curriculum it amf sized on
financial analysis risk customized
insurance sectors  It also helped me
build up my analytical and problem-
solving skills that
enabled me to undertake various projects and assignments which enabled
me to approach risk effectively and create a value-driven strategy. Can you describe the
mentoring support you received during the
placement process? My faculty mentors
provided me with personalized guidance. They were
available from me at any time and talking about it
at the time of interview. So you will
not believe I call them at night or at any time. They are
totally available for me. They also helped
me identify how did
the faculty support enhance my job
readiness? The faculty at FIB made me sure that I was well
prepared for my role at
ICIC by integrating the real-
world case study. They told me what all
consequences I can face and they told me how I need to
work upon it. They also
played a significant role in boosting up
my confidence during the  Time of
interview What advice would you give to
juniors aiming for a placement in the
insurance sector So I would advise
juniors to build a solid foundation in
financial and risk analysis while also
developing their communication skills as well as
client interaction as this is the sector of
risk analysis so the client interaction will be at most that they have to
work up on It is
essential to stay updated on industry
trends regulated frameworks and yes you will
succeed What are your immediate career
goals for your first year at ICICI
Lumbard So talking about my immediate career
goals at ICICI Lumbard are to develop a deep
understanding of the company's underwriting
process as its profile writer
Contribute effectively to risk assessment
and management and deliver quality service
to clients Overall Thank You